<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dr. Osama Mahmoud</title>
    <description>Statistician with a PhD in Biostatistics, a MSc in Applied Statistics. An expert in Medical Statistic applications with an extensive programming skills, mainly using R.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Cleft Care UK</title>
        <description>
          
          The Cleft Care UK (CCUK) is a cross sectional survey of five year old children born with unilateral cleft lip and palate. It was carried out 15 years after an initial survey commissioned by the Clinical Standards Advisory Group (CSAG) led to government recommendations on centralisation. CCUK was a multi-centre...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016-12-09-CCUK/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016-12-09-CCUK/</guid>
        
		  
		    <category>Multilevel-modelling</category>
		  
		    <category>Children-craniofacial</category>
		  
		    <category>Ongoing</category>
		  
		
		
		  
		
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Evaluation of Wellpoint Health Kiosk</title>
        <description>
          A Pilot Study - 
          Health screening in work has become a key issue in improving employee performance and reducing the risk of healthcare costs. Electronic kiosks, as automated tools for occupational health check, can be set up in a workplace to monitor employee well-being by providing health related information. Wellpoint have developed a range...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016-11-01-Wellpoint/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016-11-01-Wellpoint/</guid>
        
		  
		    <category>Public-health</category>
		  
		    <category>Ongoing</category>
		  
		
		
		  
		
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Math symboles</title>
        <description>
          
          The gamma funcion Γ is a special function in mathematical analysis. For complex z in the right half plane, we define \begin{equation} \Gamma(z) := \int_{0}^{\infty}t^{z-1}e^{-t}dt. \label{eq1} \end{equation} It turns out that Γ is holomorphic and satisfies Γ(z + 1)=z**Γ(z) for all z with Re z &amp;gt; 0. This is just an inline equation X + Y = 2....
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016-08-20-my-math/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016-08-20-my-math/</guid>
        
		  
		    <category>math</category>
		  
		    <category>symboles</category>
		  
		    <category>Ongoing</category>
		  
		
		
		  
		
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Test markdown</title>
        <description>
          Each post also has a subtitle - 
          You can write regular markdown here and Jekyll will automatically convert it to a nice webpage. I strongly encourage you to take 5 minutes to learn how to write in markdown - it’ll teach you how to transform regular text into bold/italics/headings/tables/etc. Here is some bold text Here is a...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2015-02-20-test-markdown/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2015-02-20-test-markdown/</guid>
        
		  
		
		
		  
		
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
